Guide to the Stanford University, Center for Latin American Studies, Records SC0185
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Records, circa 1985-2005; Accession ARCH-2010-106
  - Undergraduate Summer Field Research, Subseries 11
    - Guilherme Coello (Undergraduate) 1999 Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 94)
    - Julie Gwozdz (Undergraduate) 1999 Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 95)
    - Marisha Banister (Undergraduate) 1999 Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 96)
    - John Bilderbeck (Undergraduate) 1999 Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 97)
    - Shobha Sadasivaiah (Undergraduate) 1999 Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 98)
    - Sarah Guy (Undergraduate) 1999 Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 99)
    - 1999 URO Major Grants in Humanities Social Sciences, Natural Sciences & Engineering (Box 18, Folder 100)
    - Theadora Koller Summer 1998 Field Research Undergraduate (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Alexa Van Daam Gerrity 1998 Summer Field Research Undergraduate (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Undergraduate Summer Field Research Recipients (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Jocelyn Wiener 1998 Summer Field Research Undergraduate (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Summer 1997 Undergraduate Field Research (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Theresa Hwang Summer 1997 Field Research UG (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Heather Biery Summer 1997 Field Research UG (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Monisha Bajaj Summer 1997 Research Sociology UG (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Natasha Fain Summer 1997 Field Research UG (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Ines Barbosa Summer 1997 Field Research IR UG (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Sulggi A. Lee Summer 1997 Field Research UG (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Lila Musser Summer 1997 Field Research UG (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Angelika Rampel Summer 1997 Field Research UG (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Jamillah Sabry, Summer 1997 UG Field Research IR (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - UG Research - miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Megan Himan Summer 1996 Field Research UG (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Michael Turner Summer 1996 Field Research UG (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Jennifer Najera Summer 1996 Field Research UG (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Karen Serwer Summer 1996 Field Research UG (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - UG Field Research Applications deadline 1 March 1996 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - H & S Application for Funding for Conference Travel (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Research Opportunities (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Stephanie Dittmer Summer 1996 UG Field Research (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Laura Lynn Lee Summer 1996 Field Research UG (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Katherine Lupton Summer 1996 UG Field Research (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Sky Meltzer Summer 1996 Field Research UG (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Emily Rylander Summer 1996 Field Research UG (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Selena Saunders Summer 1996 Field Research UG (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Elizabeth Schwartz Summer 1996 UG Field Research (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Amy Slucter Summer 1996 Field Research UG No Application (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Nisha Varia Summer 1996 Field Research UG (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Summer 1995 UG Field Research Applications (Forms) (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Elizabeth Burson Summer 1995 UG Field Research Grant (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Ross Evans Summer 1995 UG Field Research Grant (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Amanda Morgan Summer 1995 UG Field Research Grant (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Nisha Varia LAS related thesis 2002 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Course Schedules, Subseries 12
    - Freshman/Sophomore Course Catalogue 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Orientation 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Orientation 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Orientation 1999 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - MA Orientation 9/98 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - MA Orientation 9/22/97 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Handbook 2001-02 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - LAS Handbook 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - 1999-00 Handbook (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - LAS Handbook 1998-99 Folder (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - LAS Handbook 1998-99 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - LAS Handbook 97-98 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - LAS Handbook 96-97 Folder (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - LAS Handbook 96-97 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - LAS Handbook 95-96 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Applications for Co-terminal A.M. and B.A. programs (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Master’s Program 2001-02 (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Bulletin Excerpts (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Course Schedule Spring 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Course Schedule Fall 1999-00 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - Course Schedule Winter 1999-00 (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Course Schedule Spring 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Course Schedule Winter 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - Course Schedule Fall 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - Course Schedule Spring 2001-02 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Course Schedule Winter 2001-02 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Course Schedule Fall 1998-99 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Course Schedule Winter 1998-99 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Course Schedule Spring 1998-99 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Spring Timeschedule1997-98 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Winter 97-98 Course Schedule (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - LAS Related Courses 92-96 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Claudio Duran – Chilean Studies Class - Spring Quarter 98 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Undergraduate Program, Subseries 13
    - UG Program 2003 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - Project 100 (Underrepresented Graduate Students Program) (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - 1998-99 Masters Program (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - Symposium Information (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - LAS Master’s Program 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - 1995-96 Master Program (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - 1996-1997 LAS Master Program (Box 20, Folder 61)
    - 1996-1997 Master Program (Box 20, Folder 62)
    - 1994-95 LAS Master Program (Box 20, Folder 63)
    - Faculty to Cultivate (Box 20, Folder 64)
    - Instructions – Suggestions to Faculty Re-Honor Code (Box 20, Folder 65)
    - LAS Faculty Affiliates Awards (teaching and Research) (Box 20, Folder 66)
    - LAS Affiliated Faculty Lists for Prior Years (Box 20, Folder 67)
    - LAS Faculty Affiliates Endowed Prof. Emeriti Info (Box 20, Folder 68)
    - Stanford Faculty Affiliated to Latin American Studies (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - General Files, Subseries 14; Subseries 16
    - Mailing List Faculty (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - LAS Affiliated Faculty (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Latin Americanist Faculty Nearby Campuses (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Terry Karl – Articles about, Awards (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Terry Karl, Order of Rio Branco (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Terry Karl (Chronology 9/98-12/98) (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - List of Tinker Visiting Professors & Nabuco Visiting Professors (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Rolodex Hard Copy Aug 99 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Rolodex Hard Copy Pre August 99 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Ingle James – Faculty member (Earth Sciences) (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Dominique Irvine (Affiliated Faculty) (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Evanleen K. Jones (Affiliated Faculty) (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Tim Josling (FRY) - (Affiliated Faculty) (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Samuel LeBaron (Affiliated Faculty) (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Anne Krueger (Affiliated Faculty) (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Helmut Krawinkler (Engineering) (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Caridad Kenna (Affiliated Faculty) (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Terry Karl – CV and Biographical Information (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Beatriz Magaloni (Political Sciences) (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Bruce Lusignan (Engineering) (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Yvonne Maldonado (Medicine) (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Pamela Matson (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - David McKenzie (Economics) (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Alice Milano (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Ronald Mckinnon (Economics) (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Hal Mooney (Biology) (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Kathleen Morrison (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Anne Firth Murray (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Amos Nur (Earth Sciences) (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Susan Okin (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Leonard Ortolano (Civil Engineering) (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Ayacucho Fellowship (Grad Students) (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Venezuela Ayacucho Foundation (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Ayacucho Report (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Fundayacucho - Reporting (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Ayacucho 243/203/204 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Ayacucho Fellowship (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Irvine Foundation (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - John J. Johnson Fund, Graduate Student Support (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Knowles Fellowship (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Mellon Foundation (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Gran Mariscal de Ayacucho (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Venezuelan Gift (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Announcements – Ayacucho Fund (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Ayacucho Fund (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Nabuco Chair: Establishment, Finance Info. Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Nominations: Nabuco Visiting Chair in Brazilian Studies (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - J. Wirth article for Safra Bank AR 3/97 (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - Brazilian Studies Information (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Nabuco Chair Report (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - Cardoso Visit (TKs File) (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - Nabuco Chair: Reporting (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Gifts - Nabuco (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - Tinker Fundraising (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Selection Guidelines for Tinker Chair (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Tinker General (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Tinker Reports 03-04 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Margaret (Mudge) Schink (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Schink Fund Reports (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Tinker Chair Reports (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence Tinker Foundation and Affiliated Faculty (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Tinker Correspondence and Affiliated Faculty (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Tinker Chair Correspondence Joint Efforts (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Tinker Proposal Due October 03 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Course Listings with Latin American content (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Affiliated Faculty CVs (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Selection Guidelines for Nabuco Chair (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Nabuco Fund (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - SAFRA (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Brazil Events and Info 96-97 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Brazil Fundraising / Background for Nabuco (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Brazil Fundraising (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Nabuco General Nominee Information (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Tinker / Nabuco Meetings - March 8, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Nabuco Chair Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Budget Information Revised July 2002 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - FLAS Award 2000-2003 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Title VI Budgets 2000-2003 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Application to the US Department of Education under the National Resource Centers and Foreign Language and Area Studies October 1999 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Title VI Proposal 2000-2003 Institutional Support Section (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Appendix B. doc Title VI (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Title VI Appendix B (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - EELIAS Reporting (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - EELIAS / Area Studies Courses List (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Title VI Reporting (Courses 01-02) (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Title VI Reporting (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Title VI 2004 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Zephyr Frank Lake (History) (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - James Fox (Anthropology) (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Naushad Forbes (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Jose Carlos Fajardo (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Paul Ehrlich (Biology) (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - William Durham (Anthropology) (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Alberto Diaz-Cayeros CV 2002 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Larry Diamond (Hoover) (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Mariano-Florentino Cuellar (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Enrique Chagoya (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Susan Cashion (Dance) (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Martin Carnoy (Education) (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Albert Camarillo (History) (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Rudy O. Busto (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - J. Gordon Brotherston (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - John Barton (Law) (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Clifford Barnett (Anthropology) (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - David Ackerly (Bio Sciences) (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Ronald Hilton (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Ron Hilton (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Thomas Heller (Law) (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Shirley Brice Heath (Linguistics) (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Donald Harris (Economics) (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Steve Haber (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Akhil Gupta (Anthro) (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Johanes Gumbrecht (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Adan Griego (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Jose Gonzalez (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Fernando Gomez-Herrero (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Gregory Scott (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Gary Schoolnik Medicine (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Ramon Saldivar (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Lucia Sa (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Jorge Ruffinelli (Span & Port) (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Michael Rosenfeld, Ph.D. Sociology (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Richard Rosa (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Diana Rhoten (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - John Rickford (Linguistics) (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - John Rick (Anthropology) (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Clark Reynolds (Rood Research) (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - William Ratliff (Hoover) (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - Karen Musalo – Expedited Removal Study (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - School of Medicine – Supporting Faculty (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - Supporting Faculty – School of Earth Sciences (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - Jose Carlos Fajardo South America Trip 1999 (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - Affiliated Faculty (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - Other Faculty CVs (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Faculty Vitae Chile Campus (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Ivonne Yarbo-Bejarano (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Carolyn Wong (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - Lyris Wiedemann (Box 23, Folder 54)
    - Peter Vitousek (Biology) (Box 23, Folder 55)
    - Virginia Walbot (Biology) (Box 23, Folder 56)
    - Guadalupe Valdez (Ed & Support) (Box 23, Folder 57)
    - Michael Tomz, Ph.D Political Science (Box 23, Folder 58)
    - Roberto G. Trujillo (Box 23, Folder 59)
    - Peter Small (Box 23, Folder 60)
    - Thomas Sheehan, Ph.D. (Box 23, Folder 61)
    - Michael P. Predmore (Box 23, Folder 62)
    - Julie Parsonnet (Medicine) (Box 23, Folder 63)
    - Amado Padilla (Education) (Box 23, Folder 64)
    - Robert Packenham (Polisci) (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Terry Karl Updated and Old CVs (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Sample Away Itineraries (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Terry Karl – Books, etc. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Kathleen Morrison (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Polisci Directory 1998-99 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Ayacucho Fellowship, Subseries 15
    - Andre De Mello E Souza (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Maria Helena Rueda (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Karen Sue Rolph (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Martin Valadez (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Lise Sedrez (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Erich Fox (Dissertation write up 2003) (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Jean Fleuriet – Dissertation Write up 2003 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Maria Rueda (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Marcelo Bucheli (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - William Fuchs (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Manuel Gomez (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Mayra Madriz (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Carlos Starmanns (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Gomez (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Toledo (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Ulffe (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Ayacucho Fellowship (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Manuel Gomez (Ayacucho 02-03) (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Enrique Ulffe (Electrical Engineering) Ayacucho Fellowship 2003 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Manuel Gomez (Law) Ayacucho Fellowship 2003 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Jordan Drewitt (Engineering) Ayacucho Fellowship 2003 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Rafael Aldaz (Summer Field Research) (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Prospective Ayacucho Fellows (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Carlos Suarez Ayacucho Fellowship (Polisci) (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Francisco Monaldi (Ayacucho Fellowship) (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Maria Angelica Hernandez Ph.D. Cand. Spanish (Ayacucho Fellowship 97-98) (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Ana Siqueira (Ayacucho 01-02) (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - John Crandon 1995-96 FLAS Portuguese/Law School (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Morgan C. Harting FLAS 1995-96 Portuguese / LAS (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Michael Hestrin FLAS 95-96 Portuguese / Law School (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - John Holland, FLAS 1995-96 Portuguese/Business School (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Mark T. Lavery FLAS 1995-96 Portuguese LASA (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Michael McGuinness 1995-96 Spanish/Law School (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - David Radel FLAS 1995 – 96 Portuguese / LAS (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Claudio Duran (Modern Thought & Literature) Ayacucho Fellowship Application 1995-96 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Katarzyna Polanska FLAS 95-96 Portuguese / LAS (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Ramon Gonzalez (Anthro) 1995-96 Ayacucho Fellowship application (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Mauricio Mora (FRI) Ayacucho Fellowship Applcation 95-96 (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Marie Angelica Hernandez Ayacucho Fellow (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Course Related List 2001-02 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate Student Work-Study Records, Subseries 16
    - Autumn Quarter (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Winter Quarter (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - Spring Quarter (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - Grant Recipients 1987 (Box 24, Folder 50)
    - Faculty Grant Recipients 1992 (Box 24, Folder 51)
    - Latin American Studies Student Thesis: Master & Bachelor (Box 24, Folder 52)
    - Enrollments 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 53)
    - Enrollments 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 54)
    - Brazilian Studies at Stanford – Handbook 1999 (Box 24, Folder 55)
    - Newspaper Clippings for Pressbook (Box 24, Folder 56)
    - Enlace (Box 24, Folder 57)
    - Enlace 2 (Box 24, Folder 58)
    - Press Book (Box 24, Folder 59)
    - Articles (Not LAS related) (Box 24, Folder 60)
    - Press BK articles ‘02 (Box 24, Folder 61)
    - Duplicate articles, etc. (Box 24, Folder 62)
    - Stores / CWA (Box 24, Folder 63)
    - DHL Worldwide Express 1996 (Box 24, Folder 64)
    - DHL Worldwide Express 1995 (Box 24, Folder 65)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2011-071
  - Labor Market Reform in Latin America 1/5, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Labor Market Reform in Latin America 2/5, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Labor Market Reform in Latin America 3/5, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Labor Market Reform in Latin America 4/5, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Labor Market Reform in Latin America 5/5, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Garifuna Peoples 1/5, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Garifuna Peoples 2/5, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Garifuna Peoples 3/5, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Garifuna Peoples 4/5, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Garifuna Peoples 5/5, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Central American Indigenous Art Bibliography 1/4, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Central American Indigenous Art Bibliography 2/4, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Central American Indigenous Art Bibliography 3/4, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Central American Indigenous Art Bibliography 4/4, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "From Frei to Frei: Perspectives on Chile over Three Decades" 1/12, 1997 Apr 24-26 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "From Frei to Frei: Perspectives on Chile over Three Decades" 2/12, 1997 Apr 24-26 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "From Frei to Frei: Perspectives on Chile over Three Decades" 3/12, 1997 Apr 24-26 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "From Frei to Frei: Perspectives on Chile over Three Decades" 4/12, 1997 Apr 24-26 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "From Frei to Frei: Perspectives on Chile over Three Decades" 5/12, 1997 Apr 24-26 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - "From Frei to Frei: Perspectives on Chile over Three Decades" 6/12, 1997 Apr 24-26 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "From Frei to Frei: Perspectives on Chile over Three Decades" 7/12, 1997 Apr 24-26 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "From Frei to Frei: Perspectives on Chile over Three Decades" 8/12, 1997 Apr 24-26 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "From Frei to Frei: Perspectives on Chile over Three Decades" 9/12, 1997 Apr 24-26 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - "From Frei to Frei: Perspectives on Chile over Three Decades" 10/12, 1997 Apr 24-26 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "From Frei to Frei: Perspectives on Chile over Three Decades" 11/12, 1997 Apr 24-26 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "From Frei to Frei: Perspectives on Chile over Three Decades" 12/12, 1997 Apr 24-26 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Mexican Digital Archive - Communication Contacts 1/5, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Mexican Digital Archive - Communication Contacts 2/5, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Mexican Digital Archive - Communication Contacts 3/5, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Mexican Digital Archive - Communication Contacts 4/5, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Mexican Digital Archive - Communication Contacts 5/5, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Negotiating Rights in Brazil 1/7, 1996 Oct 21-22 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Negotiating Rights in Brazil 2/7, 1996 Oct 21-22 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Negotiating Rights in Brazil 3/7, 1996 Oct 21-22 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Negotiating Rights in Brazil 4/7, 1996 Oct 21-22 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Negotiating Rights in Brazil 5/7, 1996 Oct 21-22 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Negotiating Rights in Brazil 6/7, 1996 Oct 21-22 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Negotiating Rights in Brazil 7/7, 1996 Oct 21-22 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Chile Conference, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Mayors Conference Binder #1 1/3, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Mayors Conference Binder #1 2/3, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Mayors Conference Binder #1 3/3, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Mayors Conference Binder #2 1/3, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Mayors Conference Binder #2 2/3, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Mayors Conference Binder #2 3/3, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Mayors Conference, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Press Clippings - Cardosa Visit 1/3, 35125 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Press Clippings - Cardosa Visit 2/3, 1996 Oct 21-22 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Press Clippings - Cardosa Visit 3/3, 1996 Oct 21-22 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Press - Cardosa Visit, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Mayors Conference Participants Info - Non-Attendees 1/5, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Mayors Conference Participants Info - Non-Attendees 2/5, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Mayors Conference Participants Info - Non-Attendees 3/5, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Mayors Conference Participants Info - Non-Attendees 4/5, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Mayors Conference Participants Info - Non-Attendees 5/5, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Mayors Conference Participants Info 1/4, 36161 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Mayors Conference Participants Info 2/4, 36161 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Mayors Conference Participants Info 3/4, 36161 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Mayors Conference Participants Info 4/4, 36161 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - President Cardoso Visit 1/4, 35135 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - President Cardoso Visit 2/4, 35135 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - President Cardoso Visit 3/4, 35135 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - President Cardoso Visit 4/4, 35135 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Sandstone and Tile, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Archival Articles: CLAS 1/5, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Archival Articles: CLAS 2/5, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Archival Articles: CLAS 3/5, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Archival Articles: CLAS 4/5, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Archival Articles: CLAS 5/5, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Example Website, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Example Website, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - LAS News at Stanford, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Latin America in the News 1/8, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Latin America in the News 2/8, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Latin America in the News 3/8, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Latin America in the News 4/8, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Latin America in the News 5/8, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Latin America in the News 6/8, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Latin America in the News 7/8, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Latin America in the News 8/8, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Latin America in the News 1/4, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Latin America in the News 2/4, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Latin America in the News 3/4, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 12)